Kum.
I want to go public.
Is that a good idea, Anda?
Your family isn't okay with this, are they?
Anda.
Why did you come home so early?
You know what your dad is like lately.
Can you pretend you're hitting on me?
Okay.
I'll
hit
on
you.
Sheesh...
Is my friend about to get into a relationship?
If that's the case,
the rivalry between the two faculties is over.
Now they're two loving faculties.
I've got you this.
I think you'll like it.
Where did you get this?!
Hey...
Are those the freshmen?
Yeah.
They probably just got back from camp.
- See you.
- Let me talk to...
That kid,
what's his name?
It's Satang,
a first-year Automotive Engineering student.
Hello, hello.
How are things?
Was the camp fun?
It was.
But I almost got my face burned off.
It was scorching hot.
I thought you'd be there, too.
Us, really?
How would we even make it?
We already don't have time
to work on our project.
Gosh...
It's just a project. What's to worry about?
You're just that cool, you know?
Jinna.
I really like you.
What the hell?
That came out of nowhere.
No...
I mean,
you're my idol
in sports
and academics.
You play soccer, too?
I do.
I played for my school.
You sure you can handle it?
I'm up for any challenge.
God damn.
Satang, right?
Yes.
My name's "Satang."
A girly name, right?
When I was little, I told my mom
I wanted another name,
but she wanted to stick with
Thai currency names.
Why, though?
You've got a cool name.
Sounds like you'll make a fortune.
Tod,
what kind of currency
would I be?
"Euro?"
Handsome.
Judging by your looks,
I'd say "bottle caps"
cause it sounds like "crap."
Damn you!
You and your foul mouth.
My older brother is also named
after a currency,
but it's obsolete now.
What currency is obsolete now?
His name is "Podduang."
He's a third-year student, just like you.
Podduang from
the Faculty of Sports and Health Science?
Right on the money.
You know him?
What, seriously?!
Podduang
is interning at the soccer club.
We know him.
Really?
Damn, you know him?
Of course.
I know him well!
Podduang,
why didn't you tell me?
You get to be in the same club as Jinna,
and see him every day.
I would've joined too if I'd known.
The internship is necessary.
I'm not passionate about soccer.
No...
You know how hot Jinna is, right?
Just watching him play soccer
is a feast for the eyes
He's great at both academics
and sports.
He's simply perfect.
Dig in already,
or it'll get cold.
Right,
Podduang.
Do you know that
all the pretty girls at university
have a crush on Jinna?
I'm so jealous.
He's my idol.
My friends in the same year
also have a crush on him.
You have a chance to
be this close to Jinna,
so do some digging for me
and find out why he's so perfect
and good-looking.
Is he already taken?
Finish your food already.
You're talking too much!
[Jinna Ronnarak is calling...]
Keep eating and don't stop.
What the hell?
You just won't stop talking.
What are you doing?
What are you waiting for?
- I know...
- The food's getting cold!
Hello...
Why are you calling me?
Who are you hiding from?
Why the whispering?
Don't ask.
Just tell me what's up.
Oh...
You're afraid Satang would overhear you.
You know Satang, too?
Of course.
He introduced himself to me
as if he wanted to be my little brother.
Just ignore him.
He's got a few screws loose.
Also...
don't tell him
about our deal, alright?
Why?
Are you embarrassed?
I'm not!
I just don't want him to find out.
I actually don't want...
anyone else to do the same.
Aww...
I'm this good-looking,
and you're not going to show me off?
I only want you to pretend to hit on me.
Don't get too attached.
I don't like pretending, though.
That's not what I meant.
I only want you to pretend.
You're...
You're just that slow, aren't you?
How many times do I have to
explain it to you?
Can you stay with me
and keep explaining everything like this?
Right. I'm getting sleepy.
I'm going to bed.
Oh...
Fine.
Why the "Oh"?
You called just to mess with me.
I want to talk to you, alright?
That's it.
That's it what?
That's what I call pretending to hit on me.
Poddauang,
I told you I don't like pretending.
Right, right.
Fine.
I'll let you go to sleep, then.
Sweet dreams.
Sweet dreams, my ass?!
♫I've got feelings for you out of the blue♫
♫I suddenly fell for you♫
♫When has this become the truth?♫
♫Fallen for you without a clue♫
♫I love you through and through♫
♫Since Day 1, have I really been having a crush on you?♫
[The characters, organizations,
and events depicted in this series
are entirely fictional
and intended solely for entertainment.
The series does not endorse
any behavior depicted.
Viewer discretion is advised]
♫I once sought an answer♫
♫To what we were together♫
♫Love, as I used to see it,♫
♫Couldn't flourish without clarity♫
♫It took a long time♫
♫To realize what is important♫
♫There are no rules♫
♫To love that we wish to bloom♫
♫Simply recognizing♫
♫What your heart is desiring♫
♫Is enough♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫Nothing else matters to me, it's true♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
[Oops! Mysterious Sounds]
[Rising Star Awards]
This feels like a dream.
I dreamed of standing here,
receiving the 'Rising Star Award,'
surrounded by people who...
applauded me
and supported me.
I'd like to thank my agency
for always taking care of me.
I'd also like to thank the crew,
my manager,
and everyone who played a part
in getting me to where I am right now.
More importantly,
I'd like to thank all my fans,
both those who are here today
and...
those watching the ceremony at home.
I promise you that from now on,
I'll keep improving myself
every single day.
Your love really keeps me
pushing forward.
On top of that,
I'd like to thank my family
for always being right by my side.
Finally,
I'd like to thank my loved one
for always standing right beside me
no matter what happens.
This award is for you all.
Thank you!
[Love Anda, Team Anda]
- Anda! Anda! Anda!
Anda, can I take a picture with you?
Absolutely.
I'd truly like to thank all of you
from the bottom of my heart.
[Andaman]
Ta-da!
- Whoa!
- Congratulations, my 'rising star!'
Thank you.
Here...
Thank you very much.
- What do you think?
- It's gorgeous.
Are you tired?
I had to talk to so many people, Kum.
But you're happy, right?
Mm...
Today, I got to meet my fans.
And when I got to thank them in person,
I felt really happy.
That's good.
I'm happy for you too.
By the way...
did you have anything beforehand?
Mm.
I had dessert at the ceremony.
When we get back to our place,
I'll order you some delicious dishes, okay?
I can't wait to eat the world's largest pizza.
Sure thing.
Hey... Let me see the award!
Wow...
"Anda."
[Faculty of Engineering]
Sheesh,
our rising star is here!
Whoa!
You've got that aura.
- Look.
- I'm going blind from it.
Always with the teasing, huh?
Congratulations.
I told you you'd win the award either way.
Your name is all over
the damn media this year.
Isn't it because of the backlash?
- Hey.
- Oh?
You're overthinking it.
Where there's love, there's hate.
That's just how it goes.
At least,
there are more people
who love you than hate you
What is certain
is that we love you the most.
I'm gonna throw up.
How could you say that?
So you do know how to say nice things.
Of course.
The question is,
where should we celebrate tonight?
Not this again.
Oh, you prick.
- Enough already.
- Watch it.
So where are we celebrating?
Ask Kum to join us, too.
Well...
A friend's friend's place, then.
I'll bring Kum there, too,
so I don't have to worry about paparazzi.
You're...
so lucky to have a good boyfriend.
Well, of course.
I’m already unlucky enough to have you.
What?
This damn celebrity.
You're getting on my nerves...
- I'll kick your ass.
- Don't.
- Don't you dare.
Don't.
Jeez,
not going to say hi?
We were talking the whole night.
Hey...
Don't make it sound like that.
We were just on the phone.
That's what I meant.
How did you interpret it?
Where are you going after this?
To my room, obviously.
Satang is waiting for me for dinner.
Oh, well...
Never mind.
Tonight, I'm drinking with my friends.
Go on, then.
Why are you telling me that?
Just letting you know
in case I don't call you.
No need to wait for me,
understand?
Who says I do?
Are you full of yourself?
You're talking nonsense.
You're wasting my time here.
Lost...
You've lost it.
You like my friend that much, don't you?
That much, yeah.
Alright, alright.
Cheers
to my rising star!
Alright, cheers.
Yeah.
You just love calling me
by my award title, huh?
It's the opposite of the state
I'm in right now,
that's why I'm drinking here with you.
The series that got put on hold...
Gosh!
It can stay that way.
Your ship partner's a freak.
All he cares about is the trend.
On that day,
when he came to our faculty,
he was lucky Jinna and I
didn't beat him up.
Try brushing it off.
Announcing like that
means you respect your loved one,
your fans,
and yourself.
It's true.
Winning the award
already proves that
the community accepts you.
In the end, no matter who you are,
we're all human, Anda.
Right, right, right.
I'm trying to stop thinking about it.
But you know that, don't you?
Even though the whole world accepts me...
my family...
Enough of that, Anda...
Let's stop talking about serious stuff.
We're here to celebrate, aren't we?
You're right.
You guys,
why are you all so serious?
Come on, a toast.
I won't let you off until you're hammered.
Alright.
You're drunk. Take it easy already.
Jinna...
why don't you find yourself a partner?
Just look at mine,
he's so handsome and good...
Are you not envious?
What the hell?
Are you showing off your partner now?
I'm not.
I'm serious.
I'm
so damn fortunate
to have Kum as my boyfriend.
Do you think...
I'd be able to go on
if I broke up with him?
Why do you ask that, Anda?
Well...
I'm thinking about
the worst-case scenario.
I'll never break up with you,
no matter what.
You're so sweet...
You pass out every
damn time you take a sip.
If it weren't for me,
you'd probably be missing a kidney now.
Take care of me until old age, then.
- There, tell that to your boyfriend.
- Jinna.
I'm gonna go back to drinking now.
Thanks, Jinna.
I'll take it from here.
He might throw up in the car, alright?
Come, Anda.
Let's go home.
Careful now.
There are steps.
Come on.
Take a step.
Slowly.
[Stadium]
Tod and Art?
Where are they?
They're talking to a professor.
They'll be here soon.
I have to leave a bit early, though.
Need to take care of something.
Mm.
Go and rest up.
We're worried about you.
Podduang.
Do you need help?
It's okay, Anda.
I'm used to it now.
I think...
I need to go now.
Tell Tod and Art for me, okay?
Right.
Don't worry.
Stay safe.
Bye.
Anda!
Get some proper rest if you're sleepy.
Don't sleep in the car.
Okay.
Why do you keep staring?
No, well...
You know Jinna, right?
Of course,
you've been talking about him daily.
No, not like that.
I mean...
You know each other,
don't you?
Well, of course we do.
I'm an intern at the soccer club.
And... like...
How well do you know each other?
Is it more than just friends?
You know what?
Just get to the point, Satang.
No, well...
There's a rumor going around
at the university
that...
Jinna is hitting on
a Sports and Health Science student.
I just want to know
who it is.
My friends in the faculty say
that...
he's been hitting on you.
Right.
Listen up.
Jinna and I are just...
[Jinna Ronnarak is calling...]
I knew it!
Wow, you two are video calling each other.
Say it and make my night.
You really had to call
at the perfect time.
If this is nothing important,
I'll scold you like there's no tomorrow!
Just you wait!
Miss you...
Aren't you...
too invested?
This is nothing but a play.
Don't forget that.
Why?
Why are we only pretending?
I told you I hate pretending.
Why?
If I actually wanted to hit on you,
that wouldn't be okay?
You're...
kidding me, right?
You think?
God!
Why can't you just answer me directly?
Why do you always
answer me with a question?
On top of that,
you're making the act feel so real.
I'm simple-minded, Jinna.
Why do you have to make me feel things?
Gotcha!
You're talking to Jinna.
Huh?
What do you mean?
What?!
You finished dinner already?
Downed the whole thing.
Don't be shy.
It's normal.
A grain of rice is on your face.
Is it?
Yeah.
Wash your mouth first.
No, but...
you're probably more than just friends...
video calling like that.
Are you deaf or something?
You still haven't finished yours.
Huh?
I'm full already...
Hey.
Hey!
You're full of secrets.
What secrets?
I don't have any.
You're lying.
Come to think of it,
Anda is quite talented, honey.
I've heard that for the award ceremony,
only big-name actors
were invited.
Isn't that right, dear?
That's right.
There are...
several award categories.
Really?
I just want this award to prove
that...
I'm doing well on
the path I've chosen, Dad.
I wonder
how prestigious
your damn award really is?
Were you defending the country?
In truth,
it's just an award for showbiz people.
Worse yet...
they're all cut from the same cloth.
Honey...
When the hell
are you going to stop embarrassing me?
Why can't you just be on the right track
like Itti, your older brother?
For Itti
to rise to such a high rank in the police,
he had to achieve a lot.
That's more like it!
That’s what makes it a profession
worthy of respect and pride.
So those are the only professions
worth being proud of?
Do other professions have
no prestige or honor at all?!
Am I that worthless
for not fighting a criminal?!
You're standing here arguing with me nonstop,
and you actually expect me
to be proud of your stupid award?!
Do you know that
you are...
the problem in this family?!
I do!
I also know
that you, Dad,
never consider me part of it.
You
only consider those
you deem useful to you.
That's it!
Honey!
Anda...
Are you hurt, Anda?
Let me see.
Oh?
Anda?
I shouldn't have headed home.
I shouldn't have gone to see him.
You went there so you'd know.
So you wouldn't have to
wonder about it forever.
He doesn't love me at all.
He never has
and never will.
Don't worry about those who don't love you.
Those who don't love you...
leave them be.
Listen...
I love you the most.
You're the only one I've got left, Kum.
I know.
I won't leave you behind either.
It's okay.
Take a break, everyone.
Chop, chop.
Go, go, go.
Oh, so freaking hot...
Jinna.
You've been practicing hard today,
so I got you some water.
- For me?
- Mm.
Thank you.
You didn't have to go to all this trouble.
Trouble?
I'm happy to do it.
And...
are you...
in a hurry to go home?
I want to talk about the scholarship.
Sure thing.
I'm not in a hurry.
Want some?
No, you can have it.
Are you tired from practicing all day?
Ow!
What's with today?!
[Anda: See you tomorrow]
[Jinna: you're not coming today?]
Found you.
What?
The coach is calling?
Not him.
It's your fans. They're all waiting
to give you snacks like you're a celebrity.
You're bullshitting me.
I know
a lot of people have a crush on you,
and I'm surprised
that you chose Podduang.
But...
You're...
serious about my friend, right?
Does it seem like I'm not?
Don't know.
You're...
half-joking, half-serious.
It's not just me.
I think even Podduang is confused
with your personality.
Whatever you're feeling,
just say it.
Don't play too many games.
My friend's dense.
If you're not serious,
then don't tease him too much.
But if you are, go for it.
I'm rooting for you.
How are you getting home, Jinna?
On my motorbike, of course.
I do deliveries, so how else?
I thought you'd walk home.
Gosh...
Playing soccer is already killing me.
You want a deliveryman to walk home?
Well, you can just...
That'd be too exhausting.
Podduang.
Take care of this one, too.
And...
It doesn't matter because...
I've got delivery jobs after this.
Hitting on a girl this late at night,
no wonder you're late for work...
Why do I feel like you're jealous?
I'm not!
I haven't mentioned
who it is,
so why did you jump the gun?
Or are you...
really jealous?
Why would I be jealous?
Quit being full of yourself.
Oh?
I've been hitting on you this much,
and you're still not giving in?
Stop the act already.
No one's around.
No need to roleplay now.
Why do you always think
what I do for you isn't genuine?
Well...
That's just how our deal is.
Is it still necessary, Podduang?
Can we just ignore it?
Just get to the point already.
I'm actually going to hit on you.
No deals, no ulterior motives.
It's just me...
hitting on you.
Is that okay?
It's just me...
hitting on you.
Is that okay?
Podduang.
Podduang...
Hey!
Podduang!
Huh?
What is it?
Why were you so zoned out?
I was just thinking about stuff.
You took hours to clean that plate.
Oh...
Don't be ridiculous.
Moving on from the economy,
we turn to today's breaking news.
Tragedy strikes
as a famous TV actor
- was found dead inside a personal vehicle.
- Podduang.
- What is it now?
- For the latest updates,
- Come and see this.
- we'll go to our reporter
- What news are you talking about?
- on the scene.
This is considered
today's most shocking event.
A renowned actor who
rose to fame in a hit series,
Anda,
was found dead
inside a private vehicle
at the condo's underground
parking lot this early morning.
Preliminarily,
authorities speculate that
stress from public criticism
may have been a contributing factor
for him to take his own life.
And behind me
is the scene
where authorities are currently working.
There are police officers
and forensic investigators
carefully examining the scene.
This has sent shockwaves
through the entertainment industry.
Our deepest condolences
go out to the victim's family
and the actor's fans.
Anda? The Engineering student?
We will continue to follow
this developing story closely
and bring you updates as they come in.
Hey...
That's Anda.
Sir, sir!
Sir!
This is considered
today's most shocking event.
A renowned actor who
rose to fame in a hit series,
Anda,
was found dead
inside a private vehicle
at the condo's underground
parking lot this early morning.
[This isn't real, right?? #WhatHappenedToAnda]
[Breaking! Anda Was Found Dead Inside A Personal Vehicle]
Preliminarily,
[I can't believe he took his own life]
authorities speculate that
[Who also thinks that this is a murder case?]
stress from public criticism
[The police suspect he died of suffocation]
may have been a contributing factor
[Keyboard detectives, you need to stop]
[Anda is gone. Can you now stop badmouthing him?]
for him to take his own life.
And behind me
is the scene
where authorities are currently working.
There are police officers
and forensic investigators...
Will there be a day when my dad accepts me?
At the end of the day...
I feel like I can never truly be myself
as long as I'm still alive.
Jinna.
Do you love me?
Fuck...
I do, of course.
Who else am I going to love
if not your dumbass?
Dumbass, you say?
At least, I've still got three of my good friends.
Not true at all.
Aside from us,
there are so many people out there
who love you too.
Those who love you,
they love you for who you are.
At least that includes Kum, right?
I don't know.
I think...
I should leave.
Thanks a lot
for listening to my ramble.
Right.
Have a safe trip home.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
"Fated to die."
Anda!
Get some proper rest if you're sleepy.
Don't sleep in the car.
[Tod: Are you okay?]
[Come to the class. Being alone will mess with your head]
[Come hang out with us]
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Was there no...
phone, laptop, or tablet
belonging to the victim?
We found nothing.
We sent in a search team,
but they found nothing.
Oh,
we did find a laptop charger
on the car floor.
But it's strange.
There was only a charger,
not the laptop itself.
A laptop charger...
I think we've got a strange case here.
That's enough.
It'll be too heavy to serve.
- This is... easy.
- How could you let our son die?
It's because you never cared about him.
You never cared about him
or accepted who he really was.
It's because of you!
How is this my fault?!
I also work and bring money home.
So what?
It's just money.
Have you ever brought happiness
to our family?!
Come on...
Honey...
How is it my fault?!
You make money, and what?
- Mom.
- Does that make us happy?!
- Mom, that's enough.
- That's why it ended up like this!
You, too, Itti.
You're a police officer,
but you couldn't protect your brother.
That's why he died!
Honey!
Stop blaming it on our son.
Why can't I?
Hey...
You...
Mom,
take a seat.
Please...
Let me do it.
I'll do it...
You go and help them there.
You're Anda's close friend, right?
Yes.
My name's Jinna.
I'm Itti,
his older brother.
Right.
I've heard about you.
I must apologize for what happened earlier.
Mom was devastated.
Even now, she still can't accept it.
She lashes out at everyone around her.
I truly have to thank you...
for staying by Anda's side
while he was still alive,
until the very day he...
It was nothing.
Anda was my best friend.
Though...
I never wanted to plan my friend's funeral.
But I'm more than willing to.
If there's anything else about
Anda that I can help with,
please let me know.
I'll help.
My brother was truly blessed
to have you as his friend.
Thank you very much.
What now, Anda?
"Jinna..."
My shrimp.
My shrimp...
It's mine. I claimed it first.
It's mine.
I claimed it first.
Typical.
Always fighting each other.
Now, now, Jinna.
Don't throw shade at us,
or Podduang might think we're weirdos.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stay still.
It'll mess up my shirt.
You're always bitching
about stuff, aren't you,
huh?
You're not bitching, right?
What?
Hey, hey, hey!
You can't do this.
This shirt is a one-off.
Ridiculous, Art.
It's true.
See?
I got it from an online thrift store.
You can't get it
in this size and print anymore.
It's like destiny.
Aren't you worried...
they sold you dead people's clothes?
Maybe...
it was their favorite shirt.
Then their soul...
might come to haunt you in that shirt.
Come on,
that sounds like something
out of a horror show.
Everyone wears secondhand clothes.
How about this?
The shrimp you're eating
is also dead. Do you know that?
The spirit of that shrimp...
Are you scared of it?
Hey.
Be careful.
The shrimp spirit...
The shrimp...
It'll come and get you.
You find that funny?
Obviously.
Tod and Art are funny.
Come and have a meal with us more often.
Come on, we don't have to
fight over some shrimp.
We can order some more.
Jinna...
What is it?
Are you crying?
I'm actually fine.
I was riding the motorbike...
and the wind was hitting my face.
That's why I teared up.
Really...
Want me to wash your face in my room?
I'm actually not crying, you know?
Right.
You're not crying.
Just come with me and wash your face.
Come on.
I'll take it off for you.
Satang isn't here?
He's away.
He'll be back late.
He's been with his friends lately.
What are you looking at?
The one who wasn't crying...
You love teasing people, huh?
My friend's dead.
Let me cry for a bit, okay?
I miss him whenever I'm on the road.
Jinna.
Maybe you don't know it yet,
but I really love Anda as an actor.
He's my source of joy.
It broke my heart when
someone insulted him.
I was happy when
someone complimented him.
And when this happened to him,
I could barely hold myself together.
I just want to tell you that
if you're hurting,
just let it out.
Don't worry about how people will see you.
He was your best friend, Jinna.
Everyone understands you.
Can I hug you?
♫It started with fate guiding us to hold hands♫
♫Or when I learned your number
like the back of my hand♫
♫I never knew that you'd become my whole world♫
♫I can't keep ignoring it,
'cause everything's a blur♫
♫Caught off guard, I don't know what to do♫
♫I'm gonna tell you how much I love you♫
So what is it, Jinna?
It's a murder case, isn't it?
I don't know.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Itti.
Honestly...
do you also think...
this probably wasn't a suicide?
Kum probably has his reasons.
He probably wouldn't hurt Anda.
Leave this to the police.
Don't stick your necks out for anyone.
Amp...
Are you alright?
Why...
You must help Anda!
Do you also think
that Anda was murdered?
Then...
how about we both try to uncover the truth?
Mm.
Let's help Anda.
♫I once sought an answer♫
♫To what we were together♫
♫Love, as I used to see it,♫
♫Couldn't flourish without clarity♫
♫It took a long time♫
♫To realize what is important♫
♫There are no rules♫
♫To love that we wish to bloom♫
♫Simply recognizing♫
♫What your heart is desiring♫
♫Is enough♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫Nothing else matters to me, it's true♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
♫I rest my hands♫
♫Holding on to yours♫
♫You chased away♫
♫My uncertainty♫
♫No words were said,♫
♫But I hear you♫
♫Loud and clear♫
♫It's meant to be♫
♫Simply recognizing♫
♫What your heart is desiring♫
♫Is enough♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫Nothing else matters to me, it's true♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫
♫Just having you by my side♫
♫It's only you who I'm willing to see it through♫
♫No matter how tough the world may be,♫
♫Just hold my hand like this♫
♫And stay here right next to me♫